Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Wow!
Good evening.
The morning chimes have arrived, and it's us, the Shift Be Tubes.
We're here at Shiftbytube.
Before we get started, we'd like to choose today's MC.
Please vote for one or two of you.
Whoever has the number tag with that number on it is the MC.
Let's start the voting.
Yes, please.
Please vote for Yasumoto or Nakayama.
I'd like to vote for Ichikawa on Yasumoto or Nakayama.
Oh, I made a mistake.
Wrong.
And, you know, I just found out.
Yes, I did.
Now, I think Suzumi was there before the class.
That's right. I wasn't thinking.
Let's go to the residents.
Let's go!
Three, two, one.
Which one's more?
We haven't seen it yet.
2 is the capital.
Okay, here we go. Ready, go!
Oh, my! Thank goodness.
So, Nakayama, who had the number 2 ticket, is today's MC. Please give him my best regards.
I am Riko Nakayama, the MC for today, with the number 12. Please give my best regards.
And now..,
My name is Ayaka Yasumoto, attendance number 5. Please give me a hand.
It seems like today was very hectic, wasn't it? Yes, I had a lot of time to spare, but about 5 minutes before the start, I was suddenly sweating.
I was so flustered. I went to brush my teeth about 3 minutes before the show started.
Too late, too late. They were counting down to 20 seconds, 10 seconds, and so on.
Oh no, oh no, oh no. I remember it was always like this.
We grew up together in a surprisingly relaxed manner.
No one told us to go or anything like that.
We just took it easy. When the manager said he was going to brush his teeth, we were like, "Ei!
Are you going now? Like, "Are you going now? I'm sure it wasn't now.
Let's begin. Let's start with the 74th episode of EBITCHU's Delightful and Foul Showroom.
Thank you very much for watching the 74th EBITCHU's Hilarious and Foul-Faced Showroom today.
Thank you very much.
Yes, Ebichu's Delightfully Fuzzy Showroom is our little sister showroom.
The sister show of Ukka's showroom...
It's our little sister showroom.
So here it is, time to spread the word!
In order for as many people as possible to see this distribution
I'm going to make an announcement on the official X of Ebichu.
Please spread the word!
Since Halloween is coming soon....
I dressed up in a costume.
Just my head.
Just here.
Just like that.
I had two of them.
Matching.
Oh, Mr. Banerjee, please.
Oh, Mr. Van Horn, please.
Mr. Van Horn.
I'm playing with you.
Excuse me, sir.
Please, Mr. Banerjee...
I'll give you the other one.
Okay, then.
I'll give you the good one and the bad one.
No, no, no.
I'll give you the other side.
Thank you.
Yes, ma'am.
Spread the word.
A lot, please.
Please.
So...
Let's go to this corner.
Let's go to this corner!
Yukari Couple's Questionnaire Talk
Before the talk, we will take a questionnaire to decide what we will talk about.
Yes, that's it...
Okay, let's start with the topic this time.
Ta-da!
First of all, 1 center 2024
Yes, sir.
2After School Rock 'n' Roll Hyper 2024
Yes. 3Akita 2024
3Akita
Caravan Music
Fes 2024 4Tale of Fortune 5Birthday Party 6Should I wash my hoodie?
7Should I wash my pajamas?
No, no, no. I'm usually at all the live shows.
I'm usually so busy with the live shows that I'm buried up to about the fourth issue, but this time, when I got the script in advance...
But this time, when I got the script in advance, there were so many things that Nakayama wanted to talk about, Yasumoto wanted to talk about, and Nakayama wanted to talk about.
I had to prepare a lot of things.
It's like I'm going to be talking about our stuff for the rest of my life.
Okay, then. And it's the ultimate consignment magazine.
Talk, talk, talk?
Well, in a way, yes.
But I'm really looking forward to it.
It's going to be fun. I'm hooked.
Okay, please vote for the number of the talk you want to hear.
Let's start voting!
Please vote.
I want to do eight.
I want to do 8.
I want to do 8 cards. I've prepared about two subjects for you.
That's great. But you know, the ultimate two choices, we did it when we went out for dinner in the first year of middle school.
We all went out to eat yakiniku (barbeque) together.
It was so much fun, wasn't it?
Because Ayaka was on her feet.
There happened to be no customers in the restaurant at that time, so we stood up and said, "This way, that way.
I said, "This one goes this way, that one goes that way, and that one goes that way.
Eight, five, four, three, two, one, until the end.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Which ones did you get today? Eight!
Eight! Eight! May I? I'll give it a shot.
As I was saying, I'm addicted to the ultimate two choices.
I'm hooked. Let's see what you guys can do.
The first one is, "I'm on the move 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
I'm really busy. I'm running all the time.
I'm either so busy that I have to stay under the covers 24 hours a day.
I have to sleep. Which is it?
When I'm under the covers, I'm not even sleepy, I'm fine.
I'm fine. But I can't do anything. It's not a miracle.
It's wonderful.
When you have to be on the move 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
When you have to be on the move 24 hours a day, can you do anything?
Like shopping.
I don't care where you go.
I'm always on the clock.
You're always on the move, running a little bit.
It's the ultimate.
Sir?
Yes, sir.
One, I have to be on the move 24/7.
2, I have to stay in the bed all the time.
Please vote for your favorite.
Doo-doo!
I'm surprised there are so many futons.
But you can't do anything with a futon.
You can't move a single step.
You can't even eat.
It's better to have a futon.
You can eat and play with your phone.
You know, something you put in your territory that day.
And no.
But can I use my phone on the futon?
If you left it there, it's fine.
You can't go get it.
First things first.
Oh, right.
Under the pillow.
Um.
There's water and other things you need. A game or something.
At least I can get up, but I can't get up. I can't even sit down for the rest of my life.
How do I use the bathroom? Oh, that's tough, too. I can't move around.
It's a given. Five, four, three, two, one, done.
Which is more? Which is more? Surprisingly. Oh, 2.
Futon! Futon. Futon bought it.
You're kidding? You're kidding?
Do it. I can't go to the bathroom.
That's right. You know that thing they make for campers and stuff, you know, the thing that holds it all together? Toilets.
They have something for that. You can leave it there.
Oh, you can leave that there.
You can leave it there, but you'll be stuck with it. I'm really stuck.
Well, which way are you going, Ayaka?
Oh, I'm moving all the time.
Oh, so I'm moving too?
I prefer to keep moving.
I can't stay still.
Yeah, I can't stay still.
Why not? Why do the futon people have futons?
Why? I'm curious.
There are diapers. Diapers are uncomfortable though.
They're pretty uncomfortable, aren't they?
Are you taking the overnight bus? I'm fine. You mean you're used to it?
But on a night bus, you sit down. You have to sleep on a futon.
24 hours a day, 24 hours a day. You mustn't move in this condition. You can't bend at the waist.
Isn't that pretty tight?
If you can't know, can't you even go to the bathroom? What do you mean by that?
I can't sit still. Is that what you mean?
Sure, it's flopping around... but it's still flopping around.
I'm just supposed to sprint to the bathroom like this.
Oh, that's what you're saying. You're saying I shouldn't be so calm.
Yes, it might be difficult, but it's possible.
Yes, I'm sure...
I can move my legs.
That's funny...!
You're running to the bathroom.
That's funny.
That's so funny.
Anyway...
I guess my thighs won out.
I didn't expect that.
Okay, one more time, if number 8 is chosen, one more question.
Oh, I'll do that.
You're right, for now.
We'll be doing this all the time.
Okay, let's see what you guys want to hear next.
Let's start the voting.
I think these two are going to be over soon.
I'm sure of it.
Is there a clock on this?
Certainly time.
This one....
Is this the right clock?
This one?
Seventy minutes.
That's what I'm talking about.
There were so many clocks.
Everybody pick one.
Okay, here we go.
Let's go to the divider.
Four, three, two, one.
What do you think it is? Which one did I get?
Number one!
Talking about the middle note?
You all know what I'm talking about.
I want to look back on the show properly.
Second half of October
Twenty.
Second half of October?
Early October.
Second place.
We are called mid-tone.
Chunyone
You guys have been sitting there for a long time, performing the songs of
I can't do it yet.
I haven't been able to do this live for a long time.
It's been two years, hasn't it?
Last year was the Okela Disco.
That's great, because it's a very popular event.
I'm glad you're doing it.
We've heard a lot of great feedback, but were there any memorable moments or songs?
Impressions. First of all, I really liked the costumes.
I know, Riko was so cute!
I love that pink one so much... Everyone wore pink this time, right?
They were all in pink this time, weren't they?
And some were more stylish than others...
I just asked them to make it brighter and brighter.
And then they were so frilly.
It was cute, with a floral pattern and puff sleeves, and the sleeves were really cute, too.
I don't think we've ever had a pink theme before.
I thought there were 10 different ways to do it.
Everyone had a different shape.
This time it was different.
We had our first stylist and designer.
It was a concept we hadn't worn before.
It's central, so I can wear it.
That's true.
I can't move in that.
Everyone wears long skirts.
It's hard to dance like that.
That's true. It's a rarity, isn't it?
I fell in love with her.
I fell in love with her more.
Because...
You're saying?
I'm in love with you.
What's the most impressive thing about this show?
Were there a lot of cover songs this time?
I guess so.
I don't think so.
More than usual.
There were more than usual. Fujii Kaze's songs, SMAP's and Fujii Fabric's.
Is it always one song at the opening or two songs at the end?
That's right. I was happy to hear SMAP sing.
It's not easy... but I was happy to sing a song about the nation's favorite idol.
They sang a song called "Thank You", which we hadn't really heard before because we weren't from the same generation as SMAP.
It was the first time for me to encounter that song.
I thought to myself, "SMAP really sings a lot of different songs.
My mom and brother love SMAP so much.
So I knew that song because it played on and on in the car when I was little.
I see.
So I was mostly happy.
Yeah, it's the kind of idol that everyone in the family cheers for.
You know... when I think of Mr. Smap... my own memories flash back.
I used to watch them on TV all the time.
It brings back memories.
They were the best... the best... generation...
Generation
They've gone away.
I've gone away with Kamei!
If you're in your late 30s, I'm sure the people in their 40s would have loved the songs of this generation.
It's too late for the generation.
Of course, the middle tone is the same as the whole cover, but also the solo.
Solo
It was kind of fun because I got to do a cover song, and it was the last one.
It was the last song in the medley, and we all came out from the rap part.
Parashooter by Mr. Holder.
This was the first time I heard this song. I knew the group existed, but I didn't know they had a song like this.
I knew the group existed, but I didn't know they had a song like this.
I was so happy to meet this new song, and I was so happy that all of the members liked this song because we were going to perform it live, and a lot of them said it was fun.
It was fun to do "yay yay yay" with everyone.
Riko
Five songs.
I couldn't say.
The one we covered was
Wonderful Days
Wait.
What's that? Wonderful days. Tamio Okuda is here.
Wonderful days.
The band's name is on the bill.
"Wonderful days of unicorns.
Wonderful!
I got it.
I forgot to tell you...
I forgot I've sung this song once in "Cannai Devil".
Oh, what?
I forgot.
I forget sometimes.
I was looking it up on X after the show.
Family tweeted about it.
Oh, right.
They said they once sang "Wonderful Days.
Wow.
Oh, so those of you who were watching at that cannai level got to hear it again.
I've had many opportunities to sing Tamio Okuda's songs.
That's true, I have that image of him.
During that time, I also sang at Chunyong.
That's right.
I sang.
But I don't know how to put it...
I guess it fits the atmosphere of the song, or the straightness of the song.
It always seems to fit her so well.
I always end up liking it.
The music.
Yeah, you know, it's hard to say, you know, I kind of like it, too.
It's a good encounter, to like more songs.
Yes, every time we do a solo cover, we like more and more artists.
Yes, yes, yes.
Our playlist, our favorite playlist grows.
I'm looking forward to it every time.
I hope we can do it again this year, or next year, or next year.
I want to do it!
I want to do it. I want to do it.
If you couldn't make it this time, we'd love it if you could come and visit us at Senju!
Please do.
Then, please continue.
Go on? Can we go on?
Maybe one more.
Yes, ma'am.
Then I want to hear it.
Vote for the token one. Please. Start.
The fall pollen count has been really bad lately.
Maybe I'm getting rid of it. How can you get rid of it? How can there be no more pollen?
I don't have it in the spring, but in the fall. I still have stage grass, but it's not bad at all.
No way. I feel like it's been pretty bad this year. I know everyone's talking about it.
I'm totally fine. I guess I'm immune now? Is it?
Okay, bye. Five, four, three, two, one.
It's over on its own.
I wonder what's going on.
I wonder. Number 6.
Do you know Parker? Really? You're gonna let me talk to him? Gentlemen, can I also talk about number 7?
I've been wondering how many times I should wash my hoodie this time of year... and I'd like to ask you guys about it.
Rico, by the way, how many times do you wash it? About 2 times? Three times? Even if you're not sweating.
Even if you're not sweating. I thought it was dirty when it was exposed to the air.
But even if it's just once, it's still in the air. That doesn't fit. But once, it's all over the place. Even if it's a para car. In a washing machine, for example.
Sure. So I wouldn't wash it once, but two or three times.
I don't know, how about you, Ayuka? I don't wash it often. I don't think I wash a lot.
I don't wash them very often, and if I washed them every time, the color would fade, and they would be so tired, and I think I'd like them very much, but what can I say?
I think I like it a lot, but I feel like it's a dirty hoodie that's been there for a few days.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
I don't know, I don't know. I mean, when it's freshly washed, when it's worn in a little bit, the material, the, what do you call it? The hardness of the material looks different, doesn't it?
No, I just think it's prettier like this.
It might be the same.
I haven't washed my denim pants or pants for about six months.
I feel that tension. I don't wash them in winter. Barker, too.
I don't sweat.
Yes, that's right.
Some people say they know what I mean.
Really? How long do people wash their clothes?
They are like jeans.
Some say they wash them every time.
Wow.
Jeans might not be washed every time.
I guess it's like this for everyone.
I'm fine with the smell. I can do pubic video.
And I don't allow jeans that haven't been washed for six months or so into my bedroom or living area.
There was a comment that caught my attention. I was wondering if you wash parkas now.
Now suddenly they are saying "Kim Takar". It came out of nowhere.
I was talking about Mr. Smap.
Maybe he is a few minutes late.
There is a time difference.
We were talking about Mr. Sumup earlier.
Suddenly we were talking about who's a member of who.
I'm getting a little nervous.
I got a comment that it depends on who you are, and I said, "Kim Thakur.
He was like, "I'm in the Arau camp.
It was really interesting.
It was funny.
I wonder if everyone doesn't wash their hair. I don't know. I think most of them wash their clothes twice or thrice. I think most of them wash it twice or three times.
Or they wash them every time they sweat. That's true. I wash it every time when I sweat. In summer.
And while you are at it, do you wash your pajamas? How many times do you wash pajamas after wearing them?
They are not exposed to the air, and they are very clean. Everyone who wears flag-in pajamas already.
No, I don't care how many times I have to wash them. You don't wash it all the time. It's so dirty.
But if it's winter, I might not wash the bottom pants for a week or so.
I wash the top, but once every two or three times, I wash the top, but I wash the bottom.
And, you know, the shabbier they are, the more comfortable they are.
I mean, it's different.
But I sweat when I sleep. A lot of people go home from work.
Well, it's true, you sweat in your sleep. How many times?
I come home every day, too, but my mom washes my clothes now.
I always think that's funny.
It's not something you can buy.
I know, right?
If I have to do the laundry for everyone in the family...
It's a lot of work when you have four or five sets of pajamas every day.
In winter, they're pretty thick, aren't they?
That's true.
Do you wash the fluffy pajamas every time?
They're not fluffy.
They're not firmer?
If they were, they'd fill the washing machine.
Of course it would.
That's true.
How long do you wear pajamas?
They don't wear them in the summer.
They go bare-chested, pants-only style.
Pants-only style.
Can you sleep in your underpants?
Don't you just want to tell him I can't?
I thought men could sleep in pants.
Can you? Absolutely not.
Do any women sleep in their underwear?
I don't think there are many.
I won't say if I'm wearing underwear, but underwear?
Oh, I see what you mean.
I mean, can you sleep with the least amount of clothes on?
In summer, they wear T-shirts and change them every day.
Oh.
There are men who say they can't sleep.
Any?
Well, I wear T-shirts in the winter too.
Is that a development?
I don't like the way the cloth ruffles when I put on the futon,
No matter how cold it is, I always wear a T-shirt.
I flop around in the futon like this to keep the futon warm, and then go to bed.
But when I wake up in the morning, it's so cold.
I have to live in a T-shirt once in a while.
It feels better that way.
Like I said in my comment earlier, I wear short-sleeved T-shirts and shorts even in winter.
I'm a friend.
You have friends, too.
Heh.
Interesting.
So it's each to his own.
That's right. I was definitely thinking that while writing this talk.
There will never be an answer.
There is no answer.
Well, that's all for now.
This was a funny and conjugal Aikey talk.
Yay.
Crackle, crackle.
Now, let's move on to the next part.
Next, I'm going to do a project like this.
It's called, "A joyful and conjugal birthday party.
Yay.
Yes, October 28th is my birthday!
Yay!
Yes, I will celebrate my birthday in this corner!
I'll be planning various celebrations and
Yes!
I should have said it better myself!
There are various celebration plans written in the script.
Let's do what we want to do!
Yay!
Wow!
Oh, that came out so quickly?
Don't say anything!
Congratulations!
Oh, wait, I'm so happy for you.
It's such a mess.
It's gone, like it was running away.
Surprise! Surprise!
You made me laugh with your congratulations.
Congratulations! Congratulations! I said, "Congratulations!
Right.
Oh, thank you.
For bringing it to my attention.
I'm so glad!
Happy Birthday again!
Almost four days from now.
How old are you?
I'm turning 24.
When I said I was turning 24, you said it was a good age.
I said, "That's nice.
I'm sure 24 is a lot of fun.
Looks delicious.
Congratulations!
Yes!
I'll be gone for good.
That's right.
They took it away.
So this means I can pick and choose what I want to do with this project.
There's a lot of stuff here.
I don't know what I'll do.
Reward time.
Eh, but one more thing done.
There was a birthday squash time, and then I realized it was over.
If you notice, you've cleared one.
Then I want you to do this. Celebration drawing.
Celebration drawing?
Maybe Ayaka will draw my portrait and present it to me.
Oh, wow! That's nice. It's the best present.
LOL.
Why do I say that? It's the best present.
I'm sure it's the best present.
Who is it? Where would I draw it?
Oh, this?
Yes!
Oh, yes.
Thank you very much. Wow, a portrait.
Which style do you want? Do you want a really cute cartoon type, or a realistic one? Realistic would be better.
Realistic, like a realistic portrait, OK. You mean the kind where you draw in a "sha-sha-sha" kind of way?
You have been working on Ebichu for a long time. Yes, we are running out of space, aren't we?
You can have it, right? I'll take it, I'll take it. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Let's draw Nakayama today. Yes, please be realistic.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, it is.
So you can draw anime-style pictures as well as realistic ones?
Yes, yes, I can do quite a lot.
I can do quite a lot.
Realistic drawings.
Anaga-chan, there are people who say that realistic drawings are the best.
Really?
Yes, really.
If you've been watching my videos, you might know how great I am at drawing realistic pictures.
Someone writes that I'm sure you're cute.
I'm sure they're going to be cute.
I also write that I wish you would include a message.
I might want you to put it in there for sure.
Since we're at this point...
One thing I've learned recently
You have a long tongue.
You mentioned it the other day.
Just two days ago.
Double-wide.
Good night.
And she wears eyeliner very well.
I have this color, but brown is brown.
I thought realistic brown would be better.
That's right.
I don't know.
And her eyes are really round.
I draw eyes like Wook's.
People say I'm starting to look like Wook.
Right?
You're starting to look like him.
Riko wasn't born first.
I've lived longer.
Yes, yes...
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh?
Oh!
Oh, wow.
This is gonna be a fun one, isn't it?
They're expecting you.
I don't expect it to be funny.
When you laugh.
It's funny.
The cheekbones are tight.
Toward the center.
Like this.
like this.
A man's dream
Sharp chin
and
Draw it.
It looks good. Why are you smiling?
Why are you smiling?
I'm scared. I'm scared.
It's a very small face.
It's a small face. I'll draw a small face.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'll take it home with me.
Yes, yes, yes,
It's pretty good. It's good enough to sell.
Really?
Yes, sir.
May I?
I did it!
I'm very proud of it.
I think I've captured its features.
Now, I'd like to present it to you.
Riko Nakayama real version
Dan!
Isn't she so good?
It's so shaky!
It's just that it's better than I expected.
The eyes are drawn big!
It's so cute!
I made a little mistake with Hermie, but I think I got the features right.
What are these? Zygomatic bone?
Yes, the cheekbones.
Like anpanmans.
He's 24 years old, so he's already tight.
Spunky?
I'd like to draw her cheeks.
What do you think?
I think you look a lot like her.
Like my sister.
I don't know.
I feel like I'm going to have her in 30 years, and then in 20 years.
You're right... maybe I drew her a little too maturely.
She'll be like this in the future.
This is what she's going to look like in the future.
What?
I think they have similar eyes.
Yes.
A little too droopy.
And the eyeliner is too long.
You're right, it's too long.
Well, I'll just take this and go.
By all means.
Thank you very much.
May I cut it now?
Yes, you can hang it in your living room.
I'm scared.
Let's have them worship it every day.
Like, "Wook won't eat it.
He might eat it.
It might get eaten.
We have good memories.
Then, what should we do next?
Well, there's Nakayama.
Oh!
Torifuna-san and Mayaka-chan.
So, let me present my Nakayama Aru Aru.
Yes.
Well, I'll start with an example for everyone. Riko-chan is something that everyone often says "ah" to her,
She looks sleepy. People tend to say that I look sleepy. People say that.
People really do say that. The newly appointed third principal is also Mr. Sigallon.
He asked me quite early in the day, "Are you sleepy, Mr. Nakayama? Like that.
Yes, yes.
That's what he said, wasn't it?
He always has that look on his face.
Like we're following him.
I wonder what it is.
I wonder.
Right?
It's true, Rika, when you want to talk about something you're not interested in...
She looks at me like she doesn't even know I'm here.
She makes this kind of face, and that's when she looks really sleepy.
When she's talking about something fun, she opens her mouth wide.
Does that happen to you guys? Like this.
Nakayama has this habit.
I'm always saying "eh-ba".
Uh, sure, uh...
I wonder what it is?
I wonder what it is...
It was an interview.
I'm sure there will be misunderstandings.
Everyone always says, "Let's see..." when they think about it, but...
I wonder...
I wonder why...
It's because they think in their head that it comes out as it is.
Your right hand moves when you sing.
I imitated you so much.
Who was it? Gao?
Namiko?
Contra Namiko, she imitates me so much.
Like this.
Namiko does it all the time.
That's how Riku does it.
I get it.
I don't know...
I don't know.
It's true, everyone moves their hands.
They all move their hands in different ways.
When they sing.
What's the name of the song?
I don't know.
Hmm.
Oh, they all call me by my name. I can totally understand that.
That's true.
I call Kaho-chan Kaho-chan too.
My sister's friends call me by "chan".
My sister calls me by my first name, but that's true. I think it's true.
I guess.
The only one of my generation who calls me by my name is Miminashina from WASUTA.
I'm not sure if Ruka-chan calls her by her name or by her name.
Ruka-chan calls her by her first name, "Deruka-chan. And Ririka Kodama and Ririka Mon from WASUTA.
Oh, I see. Only Wasta. That's not fair of Wasta.
Pompompompompompompompompompompompompompompompomp. Nogizaka-san's Yoda Yuki.
I call him Yuuki. The three of us who get along well with each other can call those we are close to by their first names.
That means we don't get along with them as well as they do.
No, no, it's a peculiar thing. The members too. It's true that when you first join as "chan," you can't get out.
That's why I was so shocked when Kaho-chan called Rika-chan "Maemaru" right after she joined. That's true.
That's right. But, what's that? Did you call her Maemmatte after all? Kaho-chan. I'm calling you Maemmu. Lately it's Maya-san.
Maya-chan. That's true. Everyone's nicknames change like that, but they never really change. We've always called you Rika-chan.
It's been that way since we were little.
I wonder what's left to do. It's hard to change the way we call each other. That's true. That may be true.
It's no good unless there's a trigger.
I wonder what else.
There's that one thing.
There's Riko.
Oh, that, that, it's coming out.
I can't use the tablet well.
Shall we go this way?
Hee...
Oh, look, there it is.
It's true, Riko, when you encourage your fans at a live performance, you use the names of places to encourage them.
You call out to your fans in various parts of the show, like "I'll give you my hand," and so on.
But you never say, "Riko, Osaka! But you never say, "Riko-chan, Osaka!
No, that's it. That's Omega 2 Fever.
Because when SSA was decided, what was the name of the band?
Saitama.
Let's go, Saitama. Riko, you were saying "Let's go" unusually, earlier.
I was thinking, "Let's go, Saitama. I thought, "Let's go, Saitama.
I went there, but why Saitama? I was like, "Why Saitama?
I see... Saitama, I see.
What was it? I was like, "Let's go to Saitama.
Because it is very simple, because we are going to Saitama, right?
From some family, I see.
I think it is that.
I can understand if it is SSA or SSA to go.
Why Saitama?
Certainly. In that sense, shouting the name of the place may be impressive to everyone.
Was it Saitama?
Let's go, Saitama.
But it is right, isn't it? We are going to visit Saitama Prefecture, so we are going there.
And what else?
When you make a goo, you use your pinky finger. Oh, it's true that I'm not good at goo. My pinky finger comes out. Why do you wear ears like a bear?
So, um, recently I've been working on a new choreography for Mikachu, the unidentified junior high school student,
I can't do the unconfirmed heart pose that Yuno came up with. It's true that it might be difficult for Riko. I can't do it.
Everyone's fingers are popping. I really can't do it.
Well, it's true that it's a little difficult.
But if I don't do it, Yu will get angry.
It's a little different.
Yuko says, "No, it's not like that.
I really can't do it.
I wonder why.
Is it the length of the upper part?
Is the third joint weak?
That's what it means.
It bends here, but not at the base.
Try it with a wipe.
I can't even get my thumb to retract.
Nails.
Long nails?
No, no, no, no.
Are they long? Are all your fingers long? Can I have a word? Can you just keep trying? Can I try to force it? If it hurts, just say it hurts, okay?
Oh, my God! It's hard! It hurts! It's hard!
Why do I have to cut it so hard? Why? It's too much! It's too much! It's a bit of a strain when I put my hands on it like this.
But maybe it's a joint problem? I think it's here, here, pinky and fingers.
Only my index finger. I've got a lot of pressure on all my fingers right now.
Let's try "Fu".
It's coming out.
Stiff!
So it's hard and fluffy. Does anyone else have the same problem?
I can't do it with my ring finger, because it's so different.
I'm a bear... yeah, I make ears like antennae... all the time.
I can't do it!
That's strange.
But you have a little finger in your pocket.
But you can't keep your index finger in there?
That's right.
Well, that was a Nakayama Aruka!
Thank you very much for congratulating us!
Well, that's all for now, Yuukaiji and his wife's birthday party!
Happy Birthday!
Here it is, the end of the 74th edition of the delightful and unfortunate showroom of EBICHU!
I'll be looking for some announcements, so I'll announce the final ranking.
Okay, I'd like to announce the final ranking.
Let's start with No. 5.
Thank you very much, Tomoppe.
Thank you, Mr. Naim.
Thank you, Naim.
And third place, mikirin db.
Thank you very much.
Second place, kron12.
And first place, Natsumi.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's start with the announcements.
First of all,
Riko Nakayama's birthday party will be held on October 29. The place is ZEPP Shinjuku. The doors open at 6:00 p.m. and the event starts at 7:00 p.m. It is an all-standard event.
It is an all standing event, so this year, I have gathered only the songs for the launch.
It's so nice. Every time Riko's birthday party, everyone says Settler is the best.
This time was especially great. I think it's going to be a lot of fun, so please come and join us.
Please come and join us. I'll be waiting for you. It's coming soon.
We've decided to open the theater version of "Ebisu Yakushitsu Yaku Everything Point: Parallel Stories" in theaters.
There will be stage greetings in Tokyo, Osaka, and Nagoya from November 1 to 9, so please come and see us, everyone.
I'll be traveling all over the place, so please check out the official homepage for more information.
Please check the official homepage for the different dates of the performances.
That's the end of the 74th edition of Evichu's Delightful and Husband and Wife Showroom.
We'll let you know as soon as we decide!
We have a little more time.
I'll let you know as soon as it's decided.
Quickly....
There are 100 cockroaches in the room.
What do you think?
Or a room that's haunted.
I don't like either one.
One is covered in cockroaches.
Two is haunted.
I don't like either one.
Okay, let's vote.
Isn't this the ultimate?
It's too ultimate.
Oh, no!
Which one do you like better?
Buckets are so bad. All the time.
They make rapping noises and other noises.
And the voices...
Like, "Riko-chan! or something like that.
They know my name.
They're scaring the shit out of me by naming names.
Sounds fun.
On the other hand, he eats things from the fridge.
That sounds fun.
But the cockroaches are pretty silent... or rather, they stay.
But they'll never stay 100 cockroaches.
They'll all wait in a line like this, in a parking lot.
If that's the case, isn't that generous?
Is the G's just gonna disappear when you beat them up?
That's the tough part.
You could pour boiling water on them and they'd still be alive.
But they don't move around.
Thank you for watching.
Yes, they are more docile than the ghosts, of which there are a hundred.
Okay, that's it. Voting is closed.
Voting is closed.
Which one is more?
I wonder which one is more popular.
This is the ultimate question. I don't like either one.
Number two? Is it a ghost?
Is it a ghost? Ghosts can be really bad, guys.
Let me tell you something.
I'm coming to your house today because I chose it.
Scary, scary, scary.
Which one are you, Ayaka?
Oh no...
Still?
I can't choose.
I guess I'll go with number 2. You should have given it to me. Well, okay, but, you know, number two. I guess I'm number two.
Well then, I'm done. That's all for now.
Bye bye! Take care tonight!
Good night!
Thank you for watching!